(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-01T00:09:31.077972",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
みんな！
Everyone!
速報だよ！
We have breaking news!
なに なに なに！？
What? What is it?!
なんと一番くじ
Unbelievably, an Ichiban Kuji...
「hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS」の発売が決定したんだって！
...for "hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS" has been confirmed!
やったー！
Yay!
ReGLOSSが一番くじ！？これドッキリか何か？
ReGLOSS is getting an Ichiban Kuji?! Is this a prank?
えー！でもどんなラインナップなんだろ？
Wow! But what's the lineup?
みんな！運試ししてみてね！
Everyone, try your luck!
なんと、11月13日
It will be released starting on November 13th...
木曜日より順次発売予定なんだって！
...Thursday, sequentially!
ぜひみんなチャレンジしてみてね！
Be sure to try your luck, everyone!
いぇーい！
Yay!
なんと、出来立てほやほやのサンプルをスタジオに用意していただいております！
And we have freshly made samples here in the studio!
おー！
Oh!
でも、ぽまえらにはまだ見せられないよ〜
But we can't show you guys just yet~
待て待て、ちょっとだけ教えちゃおっかな〜
Wait, wait. Maybe I'll share just a little bit~
教えて！
Tell us!
まずは、描きおろしイラストを使ったビジュアルボードがあったよね！
First, there was that visual board featuring newly drawn illustrations!
あった、あった！
Yes, there was!
イラストの背景にそれぞれにマッチしたモチーフがいろいろ入ってたよね〜
And the backgrounds had matching motifs for each of us, right?
はじめ「押忍！」って書いてあった！
Mine had "Osu!" written on it!
ちょこのっこフィギュア、ホロライブ一番くじではおなじみのやつもあったね
There were also Chokonokko figures, which are a staple of Hololive Ichiban Kuji.
あったね！
They were there!
表情がとっても可愛かった！
The expressions were so cute!
おでかけする時とかにさ、バッグに忍ばせて、一緒に連れて行ってほしくない？
Don't you want to slip them into your bag and take them along when you go out?
連れていきたい！
I want to!
髪の毛の塗分けとかグラデーションとかも、すごい小さいのに綺麗なんだよ〜！
Even the hair parting and gradient colors are beautiful, despite being so small!
可愛い！ラストワン賞っぽいヤツはなんかこう...
Cute! The Last One prize-like item is...
デカかったね！
huge, wasn't it?!
デカかった！
It was huge!
抱きしめて眠れる...
You can sleep while hugging it...
寝ちゃった
She fell asleep.
ヒントは以上です！
That's all the hints!
詳細は9月16日一番くじホームページで公開予定！
Details will be released on the Ichiban Kuji website on September 16th!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
なんと、お知らせはこれだけじゃない！
But wait, that's not the only announcement!
えー！？
What?!
2025年9月第4週より順次全国のカプセル自販機にていよいよReGLOSSの...
Starting from the 4th week of September 2025, in capsule toy machines nationwide, finally ReGLOSS's...
ガシャポン商品、ホロライブDEV_IS ReGLOSSミニCDコレクションが販売開始となります！
A Gashapon product, "Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS Mini CD Collection" is now on sale!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
こちら小さなCDのようなチャームで、CD風プレートやジャケットカードも取り出せる仕様になってます！
This is a charm shaped like a small CD, and it's designed so you can take out the CD-like plate and jacket card!
すごーい！可愛い！
Awesome! So cute!
ラインナップはデビュー曲「瞬間ハートビート」から、
The lineup starts from our debut song, "Shunkan Heartbeat"...
1st Album「ReGLOSS」など、シークレットを含む全6種！
to our 1st Album, "ReGLOSS"... with a total of 6 types, including a secret one!
どれが出るかはカプセルを開けてのお楽しみー！
Which one you'll get is a surprise until you open the capsule!
ガシャポンオフィシャルサイトでは、売っているお店を検索することもできるので、ぜひ参考にしてください！
You can search for stores selling them on the Gashapon official website, so please check it out!
ということで、一番くじもガシャポンもよろしくねー！
So, please look forward to both the Ichiban Kuji and the Gashapon!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
ガシャポンしに行こうぜー！行こう行こう！
Let's go do some Gashapon! Let's go, let's go!
このあとは、ReGLOSS 2周年記念配信！
Up next is the ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary celebration stream!
いったい何が起こるんだ！？たのちみー！
Just what is going to happen!? I'm so excited!
ねー！でも配信の前に、ReGLOSSの2周年に関するたくさんのお知らせを、みんなで振り返っちゃいまーす！
Right! But before the stream, let's look back on all the announcements about ReGLOSS's 2nd anniversary together!
イェーイ！じゃあまずは記念グッズ！
Yeah! First up is the commemorative merchandise!
ReGLOSS 2周年を記念したグッズが、ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップと、全国のHMVとHMV&BOOKSの店舗で販売中です！
The merchandise celebrating ReGLOSS's 2nd anniversary is on sale at the Hololive Production Official Shop and HMV stores nationwide!
ラインナップはこちら！
Here is the lineup!
おー！いっぱいある！カラーとかめっちゃ可愛い！
Wow! There's so many! The colors are so cute!
ね、可愛い。R、ReGLOSSのね。Rですよ、トートバッグいいよね。ねー！オシャレ！
Right, cute. R, for ReGLOSS. R! The tote bag is nice too. Yeah, so stylish!
チェキ全部飾りたいね。わかる！ねー！
I want to display all the instant photos. I know, right! Yeah!
ランダム缶バッジはHMV限定商品になっているので、ぜひ全国のHMVとHMV&BOOKSにお越しください！
Since the random button badges are HMV exclusive items, please visit HMV and HMV&BOOKS stores nationwide!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
そんなHMVとHMV&BOOKSで本日から開催中の、「ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversaryフェア」についても、おさらいです！
And at those HMV and HMV&BOOKS stores, starting today, here's a quick recap of the "ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary Fair"!
今回のフェアでは、ホロライブグッズを税込2200円お買い上げごとに、
At this fair, for every 2,200 yen (tax incl.) spent on Hololive merchandise...
限定クリアカードをランダムで1枚プレゼントしちゃいます！
you will receive one random limited-edition clear card!
フェアは10月5日まで！みんな楽しんでね！楽しんでねー！
The fair runs until October 5th! Everyone, have fun! Enjoy!
そして、2周年記念のボイスも販売中です！
Additionally, 2nd anniversary voices are also on sale!
今回は「旅」をコンセプトにしたボイスで、「シチュエーションボイス」と「掛け合いボイスドラマ」の2種類があります！
This time, the voices are themed around "travel," featuring "situation voices" and a "collaborative voice drama"!
例えば、旅行の準備をしてる様子であったりとか、
For example, scenes like preparing for a trip...
あとは移動中の様子なんかをね、ReGLOSSと一緒に旅のワクワクを味わえること間違いなしのボイスとなっております！
or traveling together. It's definitely a voice pack where you can share the excitement of travel with ReGLOSS!
ぜひ、何度も聞いて楽しんでください！楽しんでね！
Please listen to it over and over and enjoy! Enjoy!
いや、まさからでんちゃんが旅行前にあんなことするなんて...確かにね。柄にないことしちゃったな。だよね。
Man, I can't believe Raden would do something like that before a trip... True. I ended up doing something out of character. Right.
はい、ということで、ReGLOSSの2周年は超・超・超盛りだくさん！GLOSSERもそうでない人も、みなさんで盛り上がっちゃいましょう！
Alright! So as you can see, ReGLOSS's 2nd anniversary is super, super packed! GLOSSERs and non-GLOSSERs alike, let's all get hyped up together!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
このあとの2周年記念配信でも、何やら特大の発表があるとか！？
And we heard there might be a huge announcement during the 2nd anniversary celebration stream?!
心当たりがなさすぎる...心当たりあって！？
I have absolutely no idea what it is... You've got to have some clue?!
すんごい特大のあれだよあれ！そう！
It's that super huge thing, you know! Yes!
みなさん、最後まで絶対に、見逃さないようにしてね！
Everyone, make sure you don't miss a single moment until the very end!
それでは、配信スタートまでもう少々お待ちくださーい！
Well then, please wait just a little longer until the stream starts!
せーの、ReGLOSSでしたー！バイバーイ！
One, two... We were ReGLOSS! Bye-bye!
ソーセージが... ソーセージが...
Sausages... Sausages...
何何？
What is it?
みんな気をつけて！
Everyone, watch out!
なんかめっちゃ耳鳴りうるさいんだけど
My ears are ringing like crazy!
何やこれ
What is this?
らでんちゃんじゃない？
Is that Raden-chan?
なんか食べてない？逆に
Wait, are you eating something?
らでん？
Raden?
そんな... ほうじ茶の海なんて...
A sea of... hojicha...
泳げないよ
I can't swim in that!
待って、気をつけてね、なんか
Wait, be careful, because...
今目の前に「後ろを振り向いてはいけない 席を立ってはいけない」って書いてある
It says, "Do not look back. Do not stand up from your seat" right in front of me!
書いてあるわ
It is indeed written there.
もしかしたら振り向いたら... 死ぬかも！
If we look back... we might die!
試してみようぜ！
Let's test it out!
はいはいはい
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
じゃあ奏試してみて
Then Kanade, try it out.
これまだ夢か？夢っぽいなこれまだ
Is this still a dream? This feels like a dream.
夢じゃないよ
It's not a dream.
ていうか、あ！なんか出てきたよ！
Wait, look! Something appeared!
おい、何？
Hey, what?
えっと、読み上げるね
Um, let me read it out.
聞こえますか...... ReGLOSSのみなさん......
Can you hear me... everyone in ReGLOSS...
私はこの部屋に封印されたお宝......
I am the treasure sealed in this room...
今...... あなたたちの心に直接呼びかけています......
Now... I am speaking directly into your hearts...
何だって？
What did you say?
今から、あなたたちに2年目最後の試練を与えます......
From now on, I will give you the final trial of your second year...
お、試練
Oh, a trial.
みなさんで謎を解いて、3年目への扉を開けてください
Solve the puzzle together and open the door to your third year.
はい
Yes.
謎解きのルールは簡単です......
The rules of the puzzle are simple...
4文字のキーワードを見つけ出すのです//キーワード
Find the four-character keyword.
おおー
Ooh.
ただし、席を立ってはいけません......
However, you must not leave your seats...
真後ろだけは振り向いてもいけません......
And you must not look directly behind you...
ええ？
Eh?
ルールはそれだけです......
Those are all the rules...
ふむふむ
I see, I see.
キーワードがわかったら、一人ずつ順番に読み上げてください......
Once you know the keyword, read it out one by one in order...
みなさんの絆なら、必ずクリアできるでしょう......
With your bonds, you will surely be able to clear this...
ほう
Oh.
それでは、開始です
And now, let us begin.
さあ、みなさんで、3年目の扉を、開けるのです！
Now, everyone, open the door to your third year!
もう3年目始まってるんですけど
Our third year has already started, though.
そうそう、開けるも何もない
Yeah, there's no opening it.
まだ開けられてなかったってこと？
Does it mean we hadn't opened it yet?
なるほどね
I see.
じゃあとりあえず、なんか目の前にさ...
Well, for now, in front of us...
なんかあるね、これ何だ？
There is something. What is this?
なんかある！
There is something!
クロスワードっぽいのがある
It looks like a crossword.
クロスワードっぽいやつが置いてない？
Isn't there a crossword-like thing here?
あ、本当だ！
Ah, you're right!
何だろう、アンコ？
What is it, "Anko"?
アンコ？
Anko?
バラバラになった平仮名読んだだけだから、これ何も関係ないやつね
I just read the jumbled hiragana, so this has nothing to do with it.
え、これ「だー」
Wait, this is "da-"?
だー
Da-
ハッピーは「いんぐ」
Happy is "ingu"? Wait, what?
いんぐ？
Ingu?
それさ、問題じゃなくてさ、
That's not the question...
クロスワードの埋まってる部分だけ読んでない？
...aren't you just reading the filled-in parts of the crossword?
そうそうそう！
Yes, yes, yes!
そっち？
Oh, that's what you meant?
じゃあ、ちょっと一旦リリカの横の鍵の1番言うね
Then, I'll read clue number 1 for my horizontal key first.
はい
Okay.
ある飲み物を作るとき、精米歩合を50％以上60％以下で作るとこう呼ばれる//ヨコのカギ
"When making a certain beverage, it is called this when the rice-polishing ratio is between 50% and 60%."
あ、これ「吟醸」じゃない？
Ah, isn't this "Ginjo"?
何？
What?
ごめん、1ミリも聞いてなかった、ごめん
Sorry, I wasn't listening at all, sorry.
何で！？
Why?!
ある飲み物を作るとき、精米歩合を50％以上60％以下で作るとこう呼ばれる//ヨコのカギ
"When making a certain beverage, it is called this when the rice-polishing ratio is between 50% and 60%."
地米？地米酒？
"Jimai"? "Jimai-shu"?
え、でも「ぎ」から始まる言葉で「う」で終わるのだから、「吟醸」じゃないかなって思ったんだけど
But since it starts with "gi" and ends with "u", I thought it might be "ginjo" (吟醸).
え、拍手！そうなんだ
Wow, applause! Is that so?
って違う？
Or is it wrong?
え、違うかな？
Eh, is it wrong?
え、わかんない
Eh, I don't know.
でも「ぎ」から始まって「う」で終わる言葉他に知らないから、それでいいんじゃない？
But since I don't know any other words starting with "gi" and ending with "u", shouldn't that be fine?
いいじゃん、いいじゃん、書いちゃえ！
Sure, sure, just write it in!
書いちゃえ！
Write it in!
じゃあ次、らでんちゃんなんかある？
Then next, Raden-chan, do you have something?
えっと、えー、えーっとね...
Um, uh, well...
ちょっと待って、今来てる問題がガチすぎて、ちょっと今頭が真っ白になってるから、別の人！
Wait, the question I got is too hard, my mind has gone totally blank, someone else!
じゃあ、奏どうかな？
Then, how about Kanade?
えーっと、
Um...
丸1の横が、「こつはタンギング、身近だけど奥深い」//ヨコのカギ
Horizontal number 1 is "The trick is tonguing, close to us but deep."
あ、タンギング？
Ah, tonguing?
楽器でなんかタンギングだと、リコーダー
For instruments, tonguing would be a recorder?
「タ・タ・タ・タ」とかなんじゃないのかな？
Like "ta-ta-ta-ta", right?
やばい、全然わかんない
Oh no, I have no idea.
タンギング、タチツテトなのかな？
Tonguing, is it "ta-chi-tsu-te-to"?
かな？身近だけど奥深い。
Maybe? Close to us but deep.
わかった、いいこと考えた！一旦みんな自分の文章、自分の問題読んで、わかるやつは埋めよう
I know, I have a good idea! Let's all read our own questions first, and fill in the ones we know.
で、わかんないやつを相談する形にしよう
And then we can discuss the ones we don't know.
わかった！
Got it!
そうしよう、あんまり時間がなくなる気がしちゃうから
Let's do that, I feel like we won't have much time...
時間とかあるのかよくわかんないけど
...though I'm not sure if there's a time limit.
えー？
Eh?
あはは！これわかるよ！
Ahaha! I know this one!
これ、丸4がわかればいいってこと？
So we just need to know number 4?
え、奏わかったよ！
Eh, I figured it out!
お！全部わかった？
Oh! You got all of them?
いや、全部はわかんないけど、丸4がわかるから、キーワードナンバー3がわかりました！
No, not all of them, but I know number 4, so I found keyword number 3!
おー！これいいの？
Oh! Is this okay?
キーワードナンバー3はじゃあ何だったのかな、奏は？
So what was keyword number 3, Kanade?
えっと、丸4が「混ぜ混ぜして食べる料理。お好みでコチュジャンをかけて」って書いてあったからビビンバで...
Um, number four said, "A dish eaten mixed. Add gochujang to your liking," so it's bibimbap...
あ、確かに。その最後のワードの「ば」でした。
Oh, indeed. It was the "ba" from the end of that word.
「ば」？「ば」？「ば」って何だ？
"Ba"? "Ba"? What is "ba"?
ばか？何？「ば」って？
Idiot? What is "ba"?
今の段階は何も無いじゃん。
Right now, there's nothing.
まあ、じゃあ「ば」ね。
Well, so it's "ba" then.
ごめん、莉々華ね、どっちも分かんなくて。何？
Sorry, I, Ririka, don't understand either of them. What is it?
あの、4番目、「物事の具合を上手く処理すること。料理の味加減についても言う」っていうのが、ごめん、料理関係は本当に分かんない。
Um, the fourth one, "Handling the condition of things well. Also used to refer to the seasoning of food," sorry, I really don't know food-related stuff.
えええ！料理系VTuberじゃなかったの？
Eee! Weren't you a cooking VTuber?!
もう引退した方がいいかも、料理系。
Maybe I should retire as a cooking VTuber...
「物事の具合を上手く処理すること」って何？
What is "handling the condition of things well"?
調律？
Tuning (Choritsu)?
でも、味加減のことそう言うかな？味加減...
But would they say that for seasoning? Seasoning...
調整？
Adjustment (Chosei)?
舌？あ、でもなんか大文字小文字... あ、味...味...
Tongue? Ah, but somehow capital or small letters... Ah, taste... taste...
これさ、振り返っちゃいけないんだよね？
We're not allowed to look back, right?
ダメだよ。
No, you can't.
このさ、イラスト何なの？
What is this illustration?
どこまで、じゃあ、振り向いちゃいけない...どこまでなら見ていいものなの？
How far... so, not looking back... how far are we allowed to look?
真後ろを見ちゃダメって言ってた。横は大丈夫。
They said just don't look directly behind you. The side is fine.
横はいいんだ。
The side is fine.
横、えっと、莉々華？
Side, um, Ririka?
はい。
Yes.
奏側の横に何か無い？
Is there something on the side on Kanade's side?
奏側の横に...
On Kanade's side...
え、なんか、人を殺せそうなバットが置いてある。
Uh, there's like, a bat that looks like it could kill someone placed there.
バット？！あと、リコーダーもある。
A bat?! Also, there's a recorder.
バットとリコーダー？
A bat and a recorder?
バ、バットでいいんだね、それは？
B-Bat is fine for that, right?
え、なんかトゲトゲしたバット、本当に。
Like, a really spiky bat.
トゲトゲしたバット？鬼の金棒みたいな感じ？
A spiky bat? Like an ogre's iron club?
鬼の金棒？
Ogre's iron club?
なるほど、ありがとう。
I see, thank you.
自分の位置から見えてるもの...
Things visible from my position...
大体その二つ。おー...
Mostly those two. Oh...
何も分からんじゃん。
I don't get anything at all.
なんか分かんないのあった？
Was there something you didn't understand?
え、何これ、アーモンドのような香りがする危険な薬品、シアン化カリウムのまたの名前って何？
Eh, what is this, "A dangerous chemical with an almond-like smell, what is another name for potassium cyanide?"
むずいやつ来てるじゃん！滑舌が何て言ったか今分かんなかった。
A really hard one has come! I couldn't understand what your pronunciation just said.
アーモンドみたいな香りがする、危険な薬品、シアン化カリウム、またの名前は何？
A dangerous chemical with an almond-like scent, potassium cyanide, what is another name?
青酸カリとかじゃないの？危険な...
Isn't it "seisankari" (potassium cyanide)? A dangerous...
それか！きた！青酸カリや！
That's it! It came! It's seisankari!
せい・さん・か・り、か。
Sei-san-ka-ri, I see.
文字数合ってる？
Does the character count match?
合ってるわ。すごーい！ありがと！オッケー！
It matches! Amazing! Thank you! Okay!
できた？
Did you do it?
え？あとは？
Eh? What else?
あ！あはははは！うーん。
Ah! *laughter* Hmm.
分かった。
I got it.
え、莉々華のね、ヒントが、反対側の椅子の背中に書かれている文字が入るってなってて、
Um, Ririka's hint says that a letter written on the back of the opposite chair goes in,
多分莉々華の反対が番長なんだよね。
and the opposite of Ririka is probably Bancho.
だから、らでんちゃんか奏かどっちか番長の背中見れない？
So, can either Raden-chan or Kanade look at Bancho's back?
あ、らで見ます。
Ah, Raden will look.
「ん」って書いてあるよ。
It says "n".
ん？「ん」？「ん」か。
N? "N"? So it's "n".
ってことは料理の味加減のやつが、2文字目が「ん」なんだけど、それで4文字。
Which means for the food seasoning one, the second letter is 'n', and it's 4 letters.
味加減、味加減...味加減？
Seasoning, seasoning... seasoning?
料理の味加減についても言う、物事の具合を上手く処理すること。
Also refers to the seasoning of food, handling the condition of things well.
盤面処理とか...ダメだ、カードゲームの頭しか出てこない。
Board clear... No good, only card game terms are coming to mind.
4文字。4文字、ん、ん。
4 letters. 4 letters, "n", "n".
〇ん〇〇だよね？なんだろう。
It's _ n _ _, right? What could it be?
感覚？感覚？
Sensation? Sensation?
あ、分かったかもしれない！
Ah, I might have got it!
え？塩梅？
Eh? Seasoning (Anbai)?
あー！そうかも！え、すごーい！
Ah! That might be it! Eh, amazing!
塩梅？そっか、塩梅。かも、分かんない。
Seasoning? I see, seasoning. Maybe, I don't know.
あと、莉々華の最初のキーワードは「あ」かも。
Also, Ririka's first keyword might be "a".
おお！あ、ん、ば、ん、ん...
Oh! A, n, ba, n, n...
え？あっぱれ！
Eh? Splendid!
キーワードね。あ、そうね、並べたときに。
The keywords, right. Ah, yes, when arranged.
番長は、あと何が分かってない？
Bancho, what else do you not know?
えっと、4番だけ分かってないんだけど、あの、ヒントは反対側の椅子の背中だから、莉々華？の背中。
Um, I only don't know number 4, but the hint is on the back of the opposite chair, so, Ririka?'s back.
問題は？
What's the question?
えっと、ストリートダンス、クランプでの特徴的な振り付け。ストンプ、チェストポップ、あと一つは？
Um, "A characteristic choreography in street dance, Krump. Stomp, chest pop, and what is the last one?"
何だろう、莉々華の背中を見てあげて。
What is it? Someone look at Ririka's back.
おい、誰も見ねえのかよ！見てる見てる、今画面見てるから！
Hey, is no one going to look?! We are, we are, we're looking at the screen now!
待って、莉々華の背中見たらいいんだよね？そう。
Wait, we just need to look at Ririka's back, right? Yes.
「す」！「す」が入る。ダンスのやつ？
"Su"! It starts with "su". The dance one?
ストリップ？違う、それはニュグゴチョ...ス、ステップ？
Strip? No, that's nugukocho... S-step?
す、スクール？
S-school?
す、す、すみません。すみません、すみません。
S-S-Sorry! Sorry, sorry.
え、全然分かんない。
Eh, I don't know at all.
すみません、ちょっとぶった切ってしまって申し訳ないんですが、
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry for interrupting, but...
らでんちゃんの行こう。誰か私の背中に書かれている文字を読んで欲しいです。
Let's go to Raden-chan's. I want someone to read the letter written on my back.
はい。
Yes.
「び」です。「び」？ばびぶべぼの「び」？そう。オッケー。
It's "bi". "Bi"? The "bi" from ba-bi-bu-be-bo? Yes. Okay.
どんな問題？
What's the question?
えっとね、江戸時代に...
Well, in the Edo period...
宝石ラピスラズリの和名や、ガラスの昔の呼び方が含まれる
...contains the Japanese name of lapis lazuli and an old name for glass.
ガチすぎだろこれ！
This is way too hard!
問題が難しすぎて一瞬で頭パァンってなっちゃった
The puzzle was so hard, my brain just went splat for a second.
ここが「しゅ」なのか？
Is this "shu"?
美白とか美、美湖、美白
Like bihaku, or bi... biko, bihaku?
最初の一文字が「こ」なんだよね、こび
The first character is "ko", so... "ko" "bi"...
こ、こび？ こびり？ こびり、こ...
Ko... kobi? Kobiri? Kobiri...
やばい、あと10分しかないんだけど！え、わかんないじゃん
Oh no, we only have 10 minutes left! Wait, we don't know it.
こび、こ、こ... コバルトブルー？違う
Ko-bi, ko... Cobalt blue? No.
あ、でも多分これかな？
Oh, but maybe it's this?
何？番長なんかあった？
What is it? Did you find something, Bancho?
え、なんか、その、あ... いんぐってなるんだけど、しゅが入るって言ってたじゃん？
Well, it ends with "...ing", and you said it has "shu", right?
で、アームスイングかな？みたいな
So maybe "arm swing"?
おお！でも、わからん、そんな言葉知らんからな
Oh! But I don't know, I don't know that word.
なるほどね
I see.
生み出しちゃった、言葉を。生み出しちゃったか、じゃんじゃん
You just invented a word. / You invented it? Tada!
他に番長から連ちゃんでなんかヒントになりそうなものない？
Bancho, is there anything else around you that could be a clue?
一文字、この問題解ければいけるかもな、みたいな
Even just one letter, if we can solve this question we might get it.
うーんとね、4番だっけな？
Let's see, was it number 4?
リリラネの、リリナデの間にあるのは、トゲトゲのバットだったんだよね
Um, what's between the riri-rade is a spiked bat, right?
トゲトゲのバットとリコーダー。そう、トゲトゲのバットってさ、なんかトゲトゲのバット以外の言い方ってない？
A spiked bat and a recorder. Yeah. Is there another way to say "spiked bat"?
金棒 / 金棒？
An iron club. / An iron club?
間が、2文字目に「ん」が来る
In the middle, the second letter is "n".
こん棒じゃない？
Isn't it "konbou" (club)?
おお！それじゃない？こん棒。こん棒って言うよね？
Oh! Isn't that it?! Konbou. People say "konbou", right?
待って、ちょっと待って。はじめ最初の問題、自分で書いて間違ってる説ある？
Wait, wait a second. Is there a chance Hajime wrote her first answer wrong?
え、ちょっと待って。それ謎解こ。え、この色で写真を加工するとエモくなりがち
Wait, wait, wait. Let's solve that mystery. If you edit a photo with this color, it tends to look nostalgic.
セピア / え、だよね？合ってるよね？ / いや、わかんない、もう
Sepia. / Right? That's correct, right? / I don't even know anymore.
え、何何何？全部読んでみて / え、元々はイカ墨のことだったって
Wait, what, what? Read all of it. / It says it originally meant cuttlefish ink.
え？モノトーンとか、モノクロ？いや、でも3文字なんだよな
Wait... monotone, or monochrome? No, but it's three letters.
で、セピアだと思って。しかも、シアン化カリウムにも繋がるし
So I thought "sepia". Plus, it connects to potassium cyanide.
うん、うん、うん。で、あの、パーティー会場で使うハンマーの...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. And then, the hammer used at party venues...
ピコピコハンマー
Pikopiko hammer (toy squeaky hammer).
うん、うん、うん、で、埋まってるんだ
Yeah, so those are filled in.
で、そのダンスのやつだけわかんないんだ<
So only that dance one is unsolved.
そう。「あ」から始まって「しゅ」がつくなら、アームスイングにはなるだろうなっていうので
Right. Since it starts with "a" and ends with "shu", I figured it would be "arm swing".
あ...一文字やん？まあ、あ...で
There's one letter left, starting with "a".
あと一文字だったら「腕」かな、みたいな
If it's one more letter, maybe "ude" (arm)?
アームってこと？ / そう
As in "arm"? / Yes.
で、それで番長のワードは何になるの？ / キーワードは「む」になる
So what does Bancho's keyword become then? / The keyword becomes "mu".
なるほど。あ、ば、むってこと？ / いや、アルバムじゃねえかよ！
I see. A, ba, mu? / Wait, isn't that "album" (arubamu)?!
アルバムじゃねえかよ！他に何があんの？ちょっと待って、逆に考えよう、連ちゃん
It's definitely "album"! Is there anything else? Wait, let's think backwards, Ren-chan.
はーい / あ、ば、むの中で、の中に入る言葉なんかあるかな？
Okay! / Between "a", "ba", and "mu", are there any words that fit?
うーん、あ、
Hmm...
あじばむ、とか？
Ajibamu, or something?
あじばむ
Ajibamu.
あしばむ、あせばむ！
Ashibamu... Asebamu (getting sweaty)!
おお！あ、あ、え？あせばむ、いいね！
Oh! Wait... "asebamu" is good!
いいねー！キーワード、ナンバー2なんですけど
Nice! Regarding keyword number 2...
ナンバー2か / うん、る、のような気がしています
Number 2? / Yeah, I feel like it's "ru".
今もうその話してるでしょ！
We are already talking about that right now!
なんでだよ！いや、なんかあれだな、難しく考えすぎてたんだな
Why?! Ah, looks like I was overthinking it.
もう、もういいかもしれない。あ、特段その、あのラピスラズリの和名がわかったとかじゃなくて、なんとなく「る」な気がする
Actually, it might be fine now. Oh, it's not that I figured out the Japanese name for lapis lazuli, I just somehow felt it was "ru".
あ、でも多分ね、こ、こびる、る、のような気がするんだけど
Ah, but maybe it's "kobiruru"... I feel like there's a "ru".
あの、ラデンがすごい問題が起きていて、何が問題かって言うと、ラデンの周りに色々ヒントがあるのはね、なんとなく分かってるんだけど
Actually, Raden is having a big issue. The thing is, I know there are clues around me, but...
目が悪すぎてさ、何を表しているのか全くわかんない。何があるのか周りに全く見えない
My eyesight is so bad, I have absolutely no idea what they represent. I can't see anything around me at all!
え、ラデンちゃんの隣には、ピストルがあるよ / ピストルね！あと、なんかもう一個ない？
Wait, there's a pistol next to you, Raden-chan. / A pistol! Is there one more thing?
なんか、なんか...
Like... like...
目が悪くてよく見えない！ / 絵画っぽいんだけど、なんか大股なのか宇宙人なのか何かに乗ってる
My eyesight is bad, I can't see well! / It looks like a painting, with someone or an alien riding something with wide legs.
これ牛じゃない、これ？ / 牛なの？広い草原みたいなところで
Wait, isn't that a cow? / A cow? In a wide meadow or something...
黒い物体と白い物体がフュージョンしてる
A black object and a white object are fusing.
いや違う違う、人が大股に乗ってんじゃない、これ？ / ありがとう
No, no, isn't a person riding it with legs apart? / Thank you.
やばい、キーワードナンバー2言ってるの、る、です<
Oh no, keyword number 2 is indeed "ru".
まったく想像がつかない。だって、後ろ向けないから見えないんだけど
I can't picture it at all. Well, I can't turn around, so I can't see it!
じゃあ、もういいよね、る、で。うちらアルバムで行こうぜ！
Then "ru" is fine. Let's just go with "album"!
いや、ぽいよね、絶対アルバムだよ！それで行こう！
Yeah, it sounds like it. It's definitely "album"! Let's go with that!
じゃあ、キーワード1、あ！
Okay, keyword 1: "a"!
せーの
Ready, set...
アルバム！
Album!
どや？あ、出た
How's that? Oh, it appeared!
ど、どう？もう振り向いちゃいけないの、これ？
H-how is it? Are we not allowed to look back anymore?
まだじゃない？
Not yet, right?
振り向くよ！振り向いちゃうよ！
I'm turning around! I'm turning!
なんかある！
There's something!
ええ？！すごい！
Eee?! Amazing!
じゃあちょっと宝箱に向かってさっきの呪文もう一回唱えるか
Then, let's face the treasure box and cast that spell again.
行くよ？
Ready?
せーの
One, two...
アルバム！
ALBUM!
脱出成功！やったー！
Escape successful! We did it!
思ったより難しい問題生々しいのでやらせるな
Don't make us do such surprisingly difficult, realistic questions!
あぶねぇ！こけそうになったわ保存
That was close! I almost tripped.
怖かった
It was scary.
何これ、すごい！なんかニュー・アニバーサリーって書いてある
What is this, amazing! It says "New Anniversary" or something.
ハッピー・アニバーサリーね
It's "Happy Anniversary".
ニュー・アニバーサリーじゃない！ハッピー・アニバーサリーね
It's not "New Anniversary"! It's "Happy Anniversary"!
この配信前にスタッフさんが「いや、簡単。すごい簡単だから」って
Before this stream, the staff were like, "No, it's easy. It's super easy."
美術系受けてるのかと思った。びっくりした
I thought we were taking an art exam. I was shocked.
それぞれがちょっと得意っぽい分野の問題になってたのはよかったね
It was good that the questions were based on areas we each seemed to be good at.
やることなかった...
I had nothing to do...
ビビりっぱなしで終わっちゃった
I ended up just being scared the whole time.
はい！ということで皆さん、もうお分かりかと思いますけれど、まずは動画をご覧ください！
Yes! So everyone, I think you already know, but first, please take a look at this video!
[On-Screen Text: Snapshot ReGLOSS 2nd Album 2025.11.12 ON SALE]
バグ落ち...
It bugged out...
VTRの裏でちょっと喋っちゃって...
We talked a bit during the PV...
はい、ということでですね、なんとReGLOSSのセカンドアルバムが11月12日に発売決定！
Yes, so, ReGLOSS's second album is set to be released on November 12th!
アルバムのタイトルは「Snapshot」
The title of the album is "Snapshot"!
スナップ写真のように、日々の暮らしに寄り添い、共に時を重ねていけるような、そんなアルバムになっています。
Just like snap photos, it's an album that stays close to your daily life, letting us accumulate time together.
はい、今回のアルバムはホロライブ公式ECサイト限定の完全生産限定盤と通常盤の2種類あります。
Yes, this album comes in two versions: the Complete Production Limited Edition, exclusive to the Hololive Official EC Site, and the Regular Edition.
完全生産限定盤は海外のおもちゃを彷彿とさせるブリスターパック仕様で、
The Complete Production Limited Edition comes in a blister pack reminiscent of foreign toys,
CDの他に、アルバムの衣装と同じデニム風の色合いが可愛いカメラ型トレカケース、
and in addition to the CD, it includes a cute camera-shaped photocard case in a denim color scheme matching the album outfits,
リリースされたばかりのソロ曲のビジュアルを使用したソロシリーズカードセット、
a Solo Series Card Set featuring visuals from our newly released solo tracks,
そして複製コメント入りランダムプロフィールカード1枚がランダムで付いてきますよ！
and one random Profile Card with printed comments!
通常盤は全国流通もします。初回プレス限定封入特典として、
The Regular Edition will also be distributed nationwide. As a first-press limited bonus,
ランダムミニカードが1枚封入されています。詳細はSNSや今後随時発表される情報をチェックしてください。
one random mini card is included. Please check social media and upcoming info for details.
ホロライブ公式ECサイトのご予約はこの時間からスタート！
Pre-orders on the Hololive Official EC Site start from this moment!
予約ページのリンクが表示されていると思いますので、チェックしてください。
The link to the pre-order page should be displayed, so please check it out.
さらに、店舗別特典のラインナップを公開しちゃいます！
In addition, we're revealing the store-specific bonus lineup!
絵柄などの詳しい情報は、また後日公開予定です。
Detailed information like designs will be released at a later date.
また、このアルバムに収録されている楽曲はデジタルでの配信も予定しておりますので、お楽しみに！
Also, the tracks on this album are scheduled for digital release, so please look forward to it!
そして、セカンドアルバムのリリースを記念して、今年もリリースイベントの開催が決定しました！
And, to commemorate the release of the second album, we've decided to hold a release event this year as well!
期間中に対象商品をHMV&BOOKS onlineにて全額内金でご予約いただいた方の中から、
Those who pre-order the eligible product with full prepayment on HMV & BOOKS online during the period
抽選でご当選された方をリリース記念イベントにご招待！
will be entered into a lottery to be invited to the release commemoration event!
今回は、第1部「りりねね」、第2部「らではじめ」となっております。応募待ってるよ！
This time, Part 1 is 'RiriNene' and Part 2 is 'RadeHajime'. We're waiting for your applications!
待ってます！
We're waiting!
待って、そういえばさ、始め立ち、ライブ会場に向かってる途中じゃなかったっけ？
Wait, come to think of it, weren't we on our way to the live venue at the start?
あ、そうだった！
Ah, that's right!
いや、違う。違うよね？ライブ会場行く途中だった
No, wait. That's wrong, right? We were on our way to the live venue.
ということで、この後ですね、ミニライブ！本日MVが公開された「アワータイムイエロー」のパフォーマンスもあるんで、
So, after this, we have the mini-live! There will also be a performance of "Our Untamed Colors", which had its MV released today,
最後まで見てくださいね！
so please watch until the end!
まだまだ2周年記念配信は始まったばかり！ほな、急いでライブ会場に移動しや〜す！
The 2nd anniversary celebration stream has only just begun! Now, let's hurry up and head to the live venue!
いこう、いこう！
Let's go, let's go!
どういうステップそれ？
What kind of step is that?
どういうステップ？これ
What kind of step is this?
ここ本当ライブ会場に繋がるの？
Does this really connect to the live venue?
あ、開くよ
Ah, it's opening!
開いた！
It opened!
行こう行こう行こう！
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
ゴーゴーゴー！
Go, go, go!
着替えようか
Shall we change?
着替えよう！
Let's change!
着替えよう、よいしょ
Let's change. Alright.
やばい、チャック、チャックひっかかっちゃった
Oh no, my zipper... my zipper got caught.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
こうしてあげようか？
Should I help you with it?
あ、いけた、いけた
Oh, I got it, I got it.
あ、いけた！
Oh, we did it!
よかった
Thank goodness.
ジャージだからまた貸してもらおう
Since it's a tracksuit, let's borrow it again later.
そうだね
That's true.
やばい、もう変な汗かきすぎて、なんか冷や汗という冷や汗が止まらなかった
Oh no, I sweated so weirdly... cold sweats wouldn't stop.
難しかった？
Was it hard?
いやなんかね、言えば予想外だった
No, like, to be honest, it was unexpected.
なんか謎解きみたいなのが出てくるのかなと思ってた
I thought some riddle-like thing would come out.
普通に雑学というか知識系だったね
It was just normally trivia or knowledge-based, wasn't it?
知識を初めに持って来いや！
Bring the knowledge first next time!
溶けてる、溶けてる
Melting, melting...
あの青酸カリちょっと答えられなかったの悔しいわ
I'm so frustrated I couldn't answer that potassium cyanide one.
なんか、アモンにこれは青酸カリって最優先見たことあるの
Like, I've seen in Among Us before that this is potassium cyanide.
あり得る、ちょっと
That's possible, a bit.
そうね、知ってるやつあんまないもんな。うん
Yeah, we don't have many we know. Yeah.
ふう
Phew.
そろそろか
Is it about time?
何歌う？
What are we singing?
今から決める感じ？
We're deciding now?
カラオケじゃないんだけど
It's not karaoke...
カラオケノリなんだけど、何歌う？
It's a karaoke vibe, but what are we singing?
何歌おうかね
What should we sing?
踊りながら歌えるやつがいいんじゃない？
Something we can sing while dancing would be good, right?
踊りながら？！
While dancing?!
ハードル高いことするね
You're raising the bar high!
ふう
Phew.
よし、がんばろう
Alright, let's do our best!
止められない浮いた雲の上
Floating high above the clouds, unstoppable,
ベールに包まれた星待って
waiting for the stars wrapped in a veil...
流れて落ちてきた光跨がって
Straddling the light that came flowing down,
一瞬のフライト交わそう
let's share a momentary flight.
Look up! 無数の星たちが 嬉々としてステップ刻んだ
Look up! Countless stars joyfully stamp their steps.
我が物顔でなびくアイソレーション きらめき完成された色
Flapping isolation with a swagger, a shimmering completed color.
冴えない夢には青い空 花咲く笑顔が似合いそう
A blue sky suits dull dreams, a blooming smile looks perfect.
色なす無数のパレード 踊ろうよ on the twilight
A parade of countless colors, let's dance on the twilight.
流れに身を委ねて ただ漂うだけのハート
Surrendering myself to the flow, a heart just drifting along.
君だけのプレイリスト My flow 耳元まで運ぶよ
Your personal playlist, my flow, I'll deliver it right to your ears.
ドンピシャなモーション ドンピシャな気持ちと
A spot-on motion, with a spot-on feeling,
闇を照らすオーロラ 言葉選ばずにonly one
an aurora illuminating the dark, an unspoken only one.
踊っていたいずっと またとないこの日を
I want to keep dancing forever on this one-of-a-kind day.
降り注ぐプラズマ 君がいれば plus one
Pouring plasma, if you're here, it's a plus one.
色濃く映そう ビビットなハイライト
Let's paint it vividly, a bright highlight.
病みつきになるダンスダンス ハイになるまで愛す愛す
Addictive dance, dance, love it, love it till we're high.
寝ても覚めても華やぐトワイライト
Awake or asleep, the twilight sparkles.
きらめいたなら nice, nice もっと光り合いたい
If it sparkles, nice, nice, I want us to shine brighter together.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
次は！SUPER DUPER！
Next up! SUPER DUPER!
楽しんでいこう！
Let's have some fun!
苛ついた胸の奥 愛してやまないもの
Deep inside my irritated chest, what I love endlessly,
疑うことも知らないまま
without even knowing how to doubt.
そう 遂げる覚悟はできているよ
Yes, I'm prepared to see it through.
Gimme gimme daylight
Super Duper オートクチュールのシャンデリア
Super Duper, an haute couture chandelier,
陽が暮れるまで踊ろうよ
let's dance until the sun sets.
誰が何と言おうと 気にしない my 高い解像度
No matter what anyone says, I don't care about my high resolution.
研ぎ澄ますジブンだけ
Sharpening only myself,
美しく声を響かせて
let my voice echo beautifully.
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
Let's change this downcast world.
Super Duper
一喜一憂も 一期一会も急いで
Joy and sorrow, once-in-a-lifetime encounters, hurry up,
一心同体でいて
and be as one body and soul.
今宵なく恋したメロディと
With the melody I fell in love with tonight,
会えなくて 離したレプリカ
unable to meet, the replica I let go of,
名もなき君との境界線を越える play
crossing the boundary with the nameless you, play!
Super Duper オートクチュールのシャンデリア
Super Duper, an haute couture chandelier,
陽が暮れるまで踊ろうよ
let's dance until the sun sets.
誰が何と言おうと 気にしない my 高い解像度
No matter what anyone says, I don't care about my high resolution.
研ぎ澄ますジブンだけ
Sharpening only myself,
美しく声を響かせて
let my voice echo beautifully.
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
Let's change this downcast world.
Super Duper
ありがとう！
Thank you!
最高！
Awesome!
次の曲は、bvdiz！
The next song is bvdiz!
盛り上がっていく準備はできてるよねー！
You're all ready to get hyped, right?!
いくよー！
Here we go!
ドキドキ 史上最高アライバル
Heart pounding, the greatest arrival ever,
Easy breezy 歌いだせば favorite
Easy breezy, if we start singing, it's our favorite.
ドキドキ このままいたいよ nightout
Heart pounding, I want to stay like this, night out,
Easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody.
それぞれ異なった価値観 乗るスリルにのめり込み
Each with different values, getting absorbed in the thrill of riding,
笑う門には福来るって勝ち確 お決まりのスタンスから始めよう
laughter brings fortune, it's a confirmed win, let's start from our usual stance.
愉快な仲間気付けば by my side
Fun friends, before I know it, by my side,
ぶっちゃけ話 スマートに 時にハグを交わす
candid talk, smartly, sometimes sharing hugs.
運命共同体
Destined community,
伝染してゆく君の喜怒哀楽
your emotions are contagious.
分かち合えるエンパシー 共に目指すのは Reach the top, yeah!
Empathy we can share, aiming for the top together, yeah!
絶対絶対絶対絶対的キラチューン
Absolute, absolute, absolute killer tune!
今は自由気まま水色のユニバース
Now we're in a free-spirited light-blue universe,
Slowly slowly... シンクロするシグナル
Slowly slowly... synchronizing signals.
限界突破 引きつけるミラクル
Breaking limits, drawing in a miracle.
あれ？こんなところにカメラが！
Huh? There's a camera here!
みんな、写っちゃおー！
Everyone, get in the shot!
おっきい！ドキドキ 史上最高アライバル
Big! Heart pounding, the greatest arrival ever!
easy breezy
歌い出せば favorite
If we start singing, it's our favorite
okey dokey
このままでいたいよね
We want to stay like this forever, right?
easy breezy
踊ろうよ everybody
Let's dance, everybody!
ひとり募ればまたひとり 無性に会いたくなる気持ち
If one person gathers, then another... I get this uncontrollable urge to meet you
片隅のモノローグも 繋がるプロローグ
Even a monologue in the corner connects to a prologue
もう終了時間あっという間の stream
It's already ending, this stream went by in a flash
皆といる空間が extreme
This space with everyone is extreme
量産する掛け替えのない memories
Mass-producing irreplaceable memories
遮二無二 掴み取る next dream
Recklessly grasping our next dream
運命共同体 伝染してゆく喜怒哀楽
Bound by a common fate, our emotions are contagious
分かち合えるエンパシー 共に目指すは
An empathy we can share, together we aim to...
reach the top yeah
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対的キラーチューン
An absolute, absolute, absolute, absolute killer tune!
今は自由気まま水入らずなユニバース
Right now, it's a care-free, private universe
reload re reload reload シンクロするシナプス
reload, re-reload, reload, synapses syncing up
限界突破 惹きつけるミラクル
Breaking past our limits, attracting a miracle
okey dokey
史上最高な bv diz
The greatest bv diz in history!
easy breezy
歌い出せば favorite
If we start singing, it's our favorite
okey dokey
このままでいたいよね
We want to stay like this forever, right?
easy breezy
踊ろうよ everybody
Let's dance, everybody!
ということで！
So with that!
いつもの挨拶...
Our usual greeting...
大丈夫？息途切れてない？大丈夫？
Are you okay? Not out of breath? Are you okay?
いつもの挨拶から行きますよ！
Let's start with our usual greeting!
Reach for the top! We are...
ReGLOSS!
はい、ということで！
Yes! So with that!
「LUCKY MODE」と「Supa Dupa」、そして「bvdiz」、3曲を聴いていただきました！
You just listened to three of our songs: "LUCKY MODE", "Supa Dupa", and "bvdiz"!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
皆さん、盛り上がってますかー？
Is everyone excited?!
盛り上がってますかー？
Are you excited?!
お！
Oh!
盛り上がってますかー？！
Are you guys excited?!
うわー！
Whoa!
わー！
Yay!
盛り上がってますかー？！
Are you excited?!
うわーーー！
Whoaa!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
お疲れ様。 / はい、お願いします。
Good job. / Yes, please.
はい、ということで、えっとー？
Alright, so... what's next?
あ、なんか、今、Xトレンドにいるって！
Ah, apparently we are trending on X right now!
えー！すごい！
Really?! That's amazing!
すごい！
Awesome!
Xってあの、SNSですか？
X, as in that social media platform?
やばい！あの有名な！
Oh my gosh, that famous one!
それ以外ないやろ！
What else could it be?!
あははは！
Hahaha!
たくさんポストしてくださってありがとうございます！引き続きよろしくお願いします！
Thank you so much for posting so much! Please keep it up!
よろしくお願いします！
Please do!
いや、でも久しぶりにさ、「LUCKY MODE」と「Supa Dupa」歌ったね。
But man, it's been a while since we sang "LUCKY MODE" and "Supa Dupa".
しかも、今回、なんていうの？このミックスバージョンみたいなさ、
And this time, it was like... what do you call it? A mixed version like this,
そうそう！ / 「Supa Dupa」は久しぶり...
Right, right! / It's been a while for "Supa Dupa"...
あ、でも「Supa Dupa」はね、5人...
Wait, we sang "Supa Dupa" with five of us...
ま、でもさ、一応ね！
Well, but anyway!
一応、一緒に歌っていただいたんですけど
We did sing it together,
うん！
Yeah!
そう、なんかちょっと、
Yeah, somehow...
久しぶりに聴けて嬉しくなっちゃったなー！
I got so happy being able to hear it after a while!
わかる！ / 久しぶり！
I get that! / It's been a while!
え、久しぶりくらいか、確かに。
Yeah, it really has been a while.
ハーフアニバーサリー以来...
Since the Half Anniversary...
「LUCKY MODE」も「Supa Dupa」もない。
We haven't done "LUCKY MODE" or "Supa Dupa".
そうかも！
That might be true!
最後のポーズ何だったの、みんな？
What was that last pose everyone did?
これ？ / そう、これ！
This? / Yeah, that!
あ、当ててほしい！コメントで！
Oh, I want them to guess in the comments!
せーので、はい！
On three, go!
はい！
Yes!
何だと思う？
What do you think it is?
当ててみて、当ててみて！
Guess, guess!
え、社長、これマジで何？
Wait, Boss, what is this seriously?
みんなで決めたじゃん！
We decided it together!
これ！ / あ、これはわかるよ。
This! / Ah, I get this one.
これはわかる。 / これは？
I get this. / What about this?
鳴き声は？
What's its call?
ピョーピョー！
Pyoo pyoo!
いや、コケコッコーだろ！
No, it's cock-a-doodle-doo!
いや、それはニワトリだ！
No, that's a chicken!
あ、でもひよこっちゃ、ひよこっちゃ！
Ah, but it's a chick! A chick!
あ、そっか、そっか。
Ah, I see, I see.
これは分かりやすいんじゃない？
Isn't this one easy to understand?
鳴き声は？
What's its call?
ピョンピョン！
Pyon pyon!
本当に？ピョンピョンって鳴くかな？
Really? Do they cry "pyon pyon"?
あ、でもペンギンって言ってる！
Ah, but they're saying "penguin"!
おお、すごい！
Oh, awesome!
で、らでんちゃんも？
And Raden too?
にゃーーーーー！
Nyaaaaa!
悪いねこちゃんがいるな。
There's a bad kitty here.
激しめのねこちゃん。
A rather wild kitty.
可愛いですね。
Cute, isn't it?
はい、何と最後はみんなで、それぞれの動物を表現しておりました。
Yes, for the final pose, we were all expressing our respective animals.
はい、わかったかな？
Did you figure it out?
わかったかな？
Did you?
じゃあ、ちょっとここで1つ、嬉しいお知らせがあります！
Now, we have some happy news to share with you!
お！何だって？
Oh! What is it?
何と、コナミさんのBEMANIとのコラボが決定しました！
Our collaboration with Konami's BEMANI has been confirmed!
はい！こちら何と何と、こじおろし...こじおろしですよ、かきおろしのコラボ楽曲や
Yes! This is actually a newly written... wait, written by Kojiro? No, newly written collaboration song!
コナミオリジナル楽曲のカバーバージョンが、BEMANI機種に登場します！
And cover versions of Konami original songs will appear on BEMANI machines!
詳細はBEMANIファンサイト公式Xをチェックしてください！
Please check the official BEMANI Fan Site X for details!
かわいい！
Cute!
So cute!
色々ね、歌ったよね。
We sang various songs, didn't we?
コラボに際してさ。
For this collaboration.
本当に。
Really.
おしゃれで良い感じの楽曲をReGLOSSで歌わせていただいたんですよ。
ReGLOSS got to sing some really cool, stylish songs.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ぜひ、プレイして聴いてみてほしいです！ぜひ！
So please play them and check them out!
お願いします！
Please do!
なんか、ソロでもさ、こうユニットとしても歌ったよな。
And we also sang solos, as well as in units, right?
ね！そうだな！
Yeah, that's right!
なんかポディウムみたいだね
It feels a bit like a podium, doesn't it?
本当に
Exactly.
色々色々聞けると思うので、楽しみにしていいてください！
We'll be showing you all kinds of things, so please look forward to it!
はーい！
Okay!
はい、皆さん、息は大丈夫そうですか？
Now, is everyone holding up okay breath-wise?
ギリ...
Barely...
喋る？もうちょっと喋る？
Are you going to talk? Do you want to talk a bit more?
ギリ大丈夫。でもいけそう！
I'm barely okay, but I think I can do it!
いけそう？ / うん！
Think so? / Yeah!
はい！ということでね、じゃあ皆さんまだまだ、まだまだ、まだまだ終わりませんよ！
Alright! So everyone, we're not done yet, not yet!
まだまだ、なんかあるかもしれないですよ！
There might still be something else coming!
はい！ハッシュタグ、これ、これもお願いします！
Yes! Please post with the hashtag as well!
呟いてください！#ReGLOSS2周年
Please tweet! #ReGLOSS2ndAnniversary
はい、じゃあ次の曲、いいですか？
Alright, are you ready for the next song?
次の楽曲はなんと！
The next song is actually...
本日公開されたばかりのあの曲！
that song that was just released today!
うわーー！ / じゃあ、立ち位置につきますか！
Whoa! / Alright, shall we get into position?
はい！
Yes!
何の曲かな？
I wonder what song it is?
I wonder.
それでは聞いてください。アワータイムイエロー。
Now then, please listen to: Our Time Yellow.
ソラヲボエで挑む人生ゲーム
The game of life challenged with rote memorization,
言い訳めいたハートに従って
following a heart full of excuses.
現実は今半即興なプロットです
Reality right now is a semi-improvised plot.
取り憑かれるオーバーな芝居
An exaggerated performance that takes over.
世渡り上手なあのコはね
That girl who's so good at getting by,
二度と被った猫剥がせない
will never peel off her fake persona.
痛みを知ってしまった magician
A magician who has come to know pain
手の内は未だ明かせない
still can't reveal their tricks.
yellow yellow ゼロからループ 点滅するピリオド
Yellow, yellow, looping from zero, a flashing period.
yellow yellow 染まる紅い化粧
Yellow, yellow, stained with crimson makeup.
I wonder if I can make it or not
例えツキに見放されても No worries
Even if my luck runs out, no worries,
私には私がついてる
because I've got myself.
宵が醒めるまであと少しだけ
Just a little longer until the night fades...
真のアイ捉える残像
The afterimage capturing the true self.
slow and steady wins the race
次の季節を越え blooming blooming
Passing into the next season, blooming, blooming...
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please, don't stop this sound.
our time yellow yellow
let it blow let it blow
ずうっと stay gold
Forever stay gold.
our time yellow yellow
let it blow let it blow
let's enjoy the moment
Look into the mirror
絡まってる蜘蛛の糸
A tangled spider's web...
It happens all the time
踊らされたって構わない
I don't care if I'm being played.
夜を日に継いで 時間を編んで 明け暮れて
Connecting night into day, weaving time, through day and night,
Always be honest
永遠に変わらないもの
Something that will never change.
yellow yellow 手を取り合えば そこに理由は要らない
Yellow, yellow, if we hold hands, we don't need a reason.
yellow yellow 染まる紅い化粧
Yellow, yellow, stained with crimson makeup.
A smile suits you best
幾つになっても changeless
No matter how old we get, changeless.
希望 夢は人知れず
Hopes and dreams, hidden from sight.
いびつで数奇な運命や 人生ごと受け入れる
Accepting the warped, whimsical fate along with life itself.
心機一転二転三転詠んで 第五感で lock on
A fresh start, twisting and turning, locking on with the fifth sense.
右見て左見て pause 前だけ向いて go on
Look right, look left, pause, face forward and go on.
歌い続ける 24/7
We'll keep singing 24/7.
終着地点は eden or heaven?
Is our destination Eden or Heaven?
No time to waste “今”だけを信じてる
No time to waste, I only believe in "now".
最後のフィナーレまで共に進め
Advance together until the final finale.
宵が醒めるまであと少しだけ
Just a little longer until the night fades...
真のアイ捉える残像
The afterimage capturing the true self.
slow and steady wins the race
次の季節を越え blooming blooming
Passing into the next season, blooming, blooming...
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please, don't stop this sound.
our time yellow yellow
let it blow let it blow
ずうっと stay gold
Forever stay gold.
our time yellow yellow
let it blow let it blow
let's enjoy the moment
一振りのダンス、一瞬の視線、一拍の鼓動
[On-Screen: A single swing of dance, a brief gaze, a beat of the heart.]
一秒一秒が永遠に鳴り響く
[On-Screen: Each and every second echoes eternally.]
ReGLOSSが描いていく“今”を切り取った 一枚一枚の連続
[On-Screen: A sequence of frames capturing the "now" that ReGLOSS is painting.]
そのすべてが連なり 観る人の記憶に焼きついていく
[On-Screen: All of it connects, burning itself into the viewer's memory.]
2025.12.16 Tue.
[On-Screen: Tuesday, December 16, 2025]
Flashpoint ReGLOSS 1st Live
[On-Screen: Flashpoint: ReGLOSS 1st Live]
ARIAKE ARENA
[On-Screen: ARIAKE ARENA]
それぞれの光が響き合い、世界をかたちづくる
[On-Screen: Their respective lights resonate, shaping the world.]
ReGLOSSはその瞬間を音楽とダンスで伝える
[On-Screen: ReGLOSS conveys that moment through music and dance.]
イェーイ！
Yay!
ということで、みんな、見た？見た？見た？
So, did everyone see it? See it? See it?
見た！ / すごーい！
We saw it! / Amazing!
12月16日、有明、有明アリーの、ブ...
On December 16th, at Ariake, Ariake Arena, bu...
もう一回！テイク2、テイク2...
One more time! Take 2, take 2...
テイク2、テイク2、もう一回いこう！
Take 2, take 2, let's go again!
うん！
Yeah!
12月16日、有明アリーナにて！
On December 16th, at Ariake Arena!
ReGLOSS 1st Live「Flashpoint」の開催が決定しました！
ReGLOSS's 1st Live "Flashpoint" has been confirmed!
やったー！ / すごーい！
Yay! / Amazing!
すごいよ！ / 嬉しい！ / すごーい！
This is huge! / I'm so happy! / Amazing!
すごーい！すごーい！
Amazing! Amazing!
え、現地ライブってことだよね？
Wait, this means a live venue concert, right?
そうだよ！ / そうだよ！
That's right! / That's right!
しかも、めちゃくちゃデカい会場だよ！
And it's a super huge venue!
そうだよ！そうだよ、ね！ / 大変だ！
Exactly! Exactly, right?! / This is big!
夢が叶うってこと？
Does this mean our dream is coming true?
やったー！
Yay!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
応援してくれたみんなのおかげだね。
It's all thanks to everyone who supported us.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
1個目の夢が叶うかもしれないんだ。
Our first dream might be coming true.
うわー！ / 頑張ろう！ / 頑張ろう！
Wow! / Let's do our best! / Let's do our best!
はい！で、こちらのライブなんですけれども...
Yes! And about this live concert...
セカンドアルバムで描いた世界観に連動して...
it connects with the world we portrayed in our second album...
ReGLOSSの「今」を記憶に焼き付ける、というテーマになっています。
and has the theme of "burning the 'now' of ReGLOSS into memory."
つまり！まさに今の私たちの集大成となるライブでございます！
In other words, this live concert will be the true culmination of who we are right now!
イェーイ！
Yay!
そしてですね、ライブのキービジュアルも改めてお見せしちゃいます！
And also, we'd like to show you the key visual for the live concert once again!
こちらです！デデン！
Here it is! Ta-da!
うわー！ / かっこいい！
Wow! / So cool!
ね！
Right?
あの、このキービジュアルはね、ライブのテーマに合わせて...
So, this key visual was designed based on the live theme...
ライブパフォーマンス中のReGLOSSを切り取ったイメージのデザインとなっています。
capturing the image of ReGLOSS mid-performance.
へえー！ / 素敵！
Wow! / Lovely!
なんかまた、普段のReGLOSSとは違った一面な感じがしたね。
It feels like showing a different side of ReGLOSS compared to our usual selves, right?
ね、雰囲気もね。
Yeah, the vibe too.
今回のライブのハッシュタグは、ハッシュタグ「#ReGLOSS_1stLive」です！
The hashtag for this live concert is "#ReGLOSS_1stLive"!
いっぱいポストして、みんなで盛り上がりましょう！
Please post a lot and let's get hyped together!
お願いします！
Please do!
さて、さて。そんな中、皆さんが気になってるであろう...
Now, now. With that said, the ticket information that you're probably curious about...
チケット情報をね、ちょっと皆さんにお見せしようかなと思います。
I'd like to show you all now.
えー、チケット情報はこちらです！デデン！
Well, the ticket information is right here! Ta-da!
はい！えー、チケットは、S席、A席、B席の3種類です。
Yes! The tickets come in three categories: S, A, and B seats.
1次先行はこのあと、21時...
The first round of pre-sales starts after this, at 9 PM...
このあと21時からスタートです。
Starting at 9 PM tonight.
先着ではございません。抽選でございます。
It's not first-come, first-served. It's a lottery system.
焦らずに申し込んでください。
So please take your time and apply.
さらに、「会場には行けないよ」という人のために、配信チケットもご用意しました。
Furthermore, for those who can't make it to the venue, we also have streaming tickets available.
こちらも、このあと21時から販売開始です。
These will also go on sale starting at 9 PM tonight.
続いて、会場のエリアマップはこちらです！デデン！ジャン！
Next, here is the arena seat map! Ta-da!
はい！S席、A席、B席が、それぞれどこになるのかは、こちらをチェックしてください。
Yes! Please check this map to see where the S, A, and B seats are located.
エリアマップはこのあと、ホロライブ公式Xでもポストするんで...
We'll also post this seat map on the official Hololive X account later...
詳しくはね、そちらをご確認ください。
so please check there for more details.
そしてみんな！喜べ、トレンド1位！
And everyone! Rejoice, we hit number 1 on trending!
やったー！ / 嬉しい！
Yay! / So happy!
嬉しいね！ / ありがとう！
That's so great! / Thank you!
いっぱいポストしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for posting so much!
2周年も、2周年もお祝いしてくれて嬉しいな。 / ね！
I'm so glad we get to celebrate our 2nd anniversary like this. / Right?
そしてそして、ライブのグッズについては、10月10日の...
And next, regarding the concert merchandise, on October 10th...
ReGLOSSの公式配信で発表します！
we will announce it during ReGLOSS's official stream!
楽しみ！ / 楽しみ！
Can't wait! / So exciting!
素敵なグッズがいっぱいあるので、見逃さないでね！
There are lots of amazing goods, so don't miss out!
そしてそして、今回発表したライブの情報や、次回のグッズの情報は...
And also, the live concert details announced today and the upcoming merchandise info...
特設サイトにて掲載いたします！
will be posted on the special website!
やったー！
Yay!
そちらちょっと、事前に見たよね？
Wait, we actually got to preview it beforehand, right?
見たー！
We did!
え、なんで見たの？ / 見たでしょ？ / 見ちゃうよ。
Wait, how did you see it? / You saw it, right? / We checked it out.
特設サイト...
The special website...
お手洗い行ってたかもしれない。
I might have been in the restroom.
そうかもね。
That might be it.
はい、すごいかっこいいサイトなんで、是非とも覗いてみてください。
Yes, it's a really cool website, so please go check it out.
特設サイトは、えっと、「ReGLOSS 1st Live」...
To find the special website, please search for...
あ、打ち込んでんだ、それ。
Oh, you're typing it out.
検索お願いします！
"ReGLOSS 1st Live"!
今後も追加情報を更新していくので、ブックマークとチェックよろしくお願いします！
We'll keep updating it with more information, so please bookmark and check it!
お願いします！
Thank you!
現地ですって、お姉さん。
It's a live venue concert, ladies.
ね、やばいね。
Yeah, that's wild.
どうよ、みんな？
How are we feeling, everyone?
どうよ？どうよ？
How do we feel? How do we feel?
はい！
Yes!
もう、りりかはこれ、ずっとデビューの時から言ってるんだけど...
So, I've been saying this ever since our debut...
もうダンスも歌も、どっちもやっぱ自信もなかったし、得意じゃないって思ってた、りりかが...
I didn't have confidence in either dancing or singing, and thought I wasn't good at them...
ちょっとずつ、なんかそれぞれを好きになっていけていて、
but little by little, I've grown to love both of them.
で、みんなにちゃんと、その成長した姿を見てもらいたいって思ってて。
And I really want to show everyone how much I've grown.
そう、その夢が、今回のまたね、新しい現地ライブっていう場で叶うのかもしれないなって思ったら、めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
When I think that this dream might come true at this new live venue concert, I'm just incredibly happy!
ありがとう！ / ありがとう！
Thank you! / Thank you!
えーっと、えっと、
Um, well...
奏はなんか正直まだ実感が湧いてなくって...
To be honest, it still hasn't sunk in for me...
現地ライブ！？
An in-person live concert?!
本当に？本当に？みたいな。
Like, "Really? Really?"
なんか実感が本当にわかなくて。
It just doesn't feel real at all.
でも、なんかずっとさ、現地ライブしたい、したいって言ってきて、いざ決定ってなって、
But we've been saying we want to do an in-person live all this time, and now that it's actually decided...
世に出て、なんか本当に不思議な気持ち。
...and announced to the world, it feels so mysterious.
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいんだけどね。なんか、夢のようで。
I'm incredibly happy, but it feels like a dream.
なんか、逆に何も感じないような...
In fact, it's so surreal that I almost feel numb...
じわじわ後から、うわ、嬉しい！ってなると思うんだけど。
I think it'll hit me gradually later like, "Wow, I'm so happy!"
おめでとう！ / ありがとう！
Congratulations! / Thank you!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
みんなのおかげです！
It's all thanks to everyone!
番長はどう？ダンス番長。 / いや、同じくね、実感がわかなくて。
How about you, Leader? Our dance leader. / Well, same here, it hasn't sunk in at all.
その、本当なんだろう、夢見心地で、よくわからないけど、
It feels like I'm dreaming, and I don't quite get it yet, but...
でも、もうあと3ヶ月くらいしたら、 ReGLOSSの皆が目の前にいて、
...in about three months, all of ReGLOSS's fans will be right in front of us...
はい、ReGLOSS！パフォーマンス！みんなが目の前で「キャー！」ってやってくれるってことでしょ？
...and we'll perform as ReGLOSS, and everyone will be cheering for us, right?
動きも一緒に。 / ってやってくれるって思ったら、もうすっごい嬉しいです。本当に、皆様ありがとうございます。
Doing the actions too. / Thinking about everyone doing that makes me so happy. Thank you so much, everyone.
ありがとうございます。 / 嬉しいね。 / そして、デンちゃんは？
Thank you very much. / We're so happy. / And how about you, Den-chan?
はい、現地ライブってことで、12月少し早めのReGLOSSからのクリスマスプレゼントってことで、
Yes! An in-person live in December, like an early Christmas present from ReGLOSS.
現地ライブさせていただきますけれども、まさかね、まさかまさかの現地ライブで、
We're getting to do an in-person live, but I never expected us to get such an amazing opportunity.
本当にこんなありがたい機会がいただけることで、生きててなかなかないじゃない？
To get such a grateful opportunity is a rare thing in life, right?
そう、だから凄くありがたいなと思うし、嬉しいなと思いますし、今ね、絶賛レッスンでね、ライブに向けて我々頑張っておりますので、
So I'm really grateful and happy. Right now, we're in the middle of lessons, working hard for the live concert.
ぜひ、今後もね、応援してくれるととっても嬉しいです！皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
So we'd be so happy if you continue to support us! Thank you so much, everyone!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ねえ、本当にライブ嬉しいね。 / 最高だね。 / でも、そのまあライブのためってわけでもないけどさ、色んな楽曲を歌わせていただいていて、
We're really happy about the live concert. / It's the best. / But not just for the live, we've been singing various songs.
ま、今回『Our Glass Yellow』も新しくリリースさせていただいたわけなんですけれども、
And this time, we newly released "Our Glass Yellow" as well.
ちょっとその感想も話そうか、ここで。せっかくだから。
Let's share our thoughts on it here, since we have the chance.
じゃあ、逆順で行く？らでんちゃんどう？ / あ、らでんはね、MV出たじゃん？
Shall we go in reverse order? How about you, Raden-chan? / Ah, for Raden, the music video is out, right?
MV出たから、もうMVもね、色んなものが素敵なんだけど、なかでもらでんは歌詞がすっごい好きなんで、
Since the MV is out, there are so many wonderful things about it, but especially, I really love the lyrics.
ちょっとMV見て、「あ、いい曲だな」とか、MV凄いめちゃくちゃ動いていいなって思った方は、もう一回次はね、歌詞にこう注目してくれると凄く嬉しいな、なんて思います。
So for those who watched the MV and thought it's a great song with great animation, I'd be happy if you focus on the lyrics next time.
おお！ありがとうございます。 / 番長は？
Oh! Thank you. / How about you, Leader?
いや、もうとにかくリズムとメロディーが好きですね。
Well, I just love the rhythm and the melody.
ずっとやってる。 / そう、凄い疾走感があって、なんかこう、その載ってる言葉のメロディーも、
She's been doing that all along. / Yes, it has a great sense of speed, and the melody of the lyrics in it...
全部なんか、リズム良かったり、なんかこう、「ツンツン」って言ったり、なんかこう激しいやん、移り変わりが。飽きない、要所要所というかさ。
...is very rhythmic, with parts like "tsun-tsun", and rapid changes. There are many highlights that keep you hooked.
なんかもう凄い、メロディー大好きっ。
I just really love the melody!
はい、聞いてください。 / 奏は、
Please listen to it. / For Kanade...
奏はまず曲がもの凄く大好きだし、
...first of all, I absolutely love the song itself.
今日、みんなとさ、初めてMVを見たじゃないですか？
And today, we watched the music video together for the first time, right?
MVを見ると、なんか凄いカッコいい感じになっていて、なんか大感激でした。
Watching the MV, it looked so cool, and I was deeply moved.
個人的一番好きなMVシーンは、えー、
My personal favorite scene in the MV is...
こういうシーン。 / どこだろ？どこだろ？
...this scene. / Where is that? Where is that?
1番の終わりだよ、1番の終わり。 / あ、サビの終わり。 / あ、あのポーズの。
It's at the end of the first chorus! / Ah, the end of the chorus. / Ah, that pose.
そう、あそこの、ぷにょんってやってた。 / この日のために、シャンプー頑張りました。
Yes, that bouncy part. / I washed my hair extra carefully for this day.
さすが。さすが。 / りりかは、
As expected, as expected. / For Ririka...
いや、りりかもね、やっぱり『Our Glass Yellow』は凄くこう、元気になる曲じゃない？
I also think "Our Glass Yellow" is a song that really cheers you up.
テンションアゲアゲってなる曲で、凄い聴いてて楽しいし、あと、踊ってても、
It gets your energy pumping and is so fun to listen to. And even when dancing...
こうやって、はぁ、はぁ、
...like this, taking deep breaths...
って、凄いいっぱい激しいところが大好きです。
...I love how intense and energetic it gets.
多分、そんなに心配しなかったです。
Probably, I didn't worry that much.
ぜひ聞いてください。
Please check it out!
え、このサビのさ、これめっちゃカッコ良くない？ / ここ。 / ここね。 / ここ。ここ。
Wait, isn't this part in the chorus super cool? / This part. / Ah, that part. / Here, here.
ここが好きなんだけど。 / ああ、わかる。
I really like this part. / Ah, I get it.
ここ。 / ここね。
Here. / That's it.
わかる、わかる。
I totally get it.
まあね、ちょっと引き続き私たちは、アルバムに収録される新曲の練習なんかもね、めちゃくちゃ頑張ってますので、
We're continuing to work really hard on practicing the new songs for our album...
水飲んだ？ 水飲んどく？
Did you drink some water? Shall we?
何の曲かな？ 何の曲かな？
What song could it be? I wonder.
何の曲だと思う？
What song do you think it is?
何歌おうかなー！
I wonder what we should sing!
何歌おうかな
What should I sing?
ReGLOSSの曲だったら、最後は「瞬間ハートビート」じゃない？
If it's a ReGLOSS song, shouldn't the last one be "Shunkan Heartbeat"?
「シンメトリー」もあるんじゃない？
Isn't there "Symmetry" too?
「フィーリングレセプション」とかもあるし
And we also have "Feeling Reception."
水飲んでくるわ / いってらっしゃーい
I'm gonna go drink some water. / See you!
「Gestalt」だね、ゲシュタルト。ゲシュタルトもそうだし
"Gestalt" indeed, "Gestalt." "Gestalt" is one...
アワータイムシリーズも出ましたしね
And the "Our Time" series is out as well.
立ち位置つきましょうか
Shall we get into our positions?
Let's get in position.
こっちということは...
Since we are over here...
こっちということは、分かる人には多分分かっちゃうかもしれない
Since we are over here, those who know might already know!
うちだけだと思う。立ち位置がここということは、みたいな。
I think it's just us who know. Like, "Oh, our positions are here so..."
はい、それでは
Alright then...
聴いてください、ミッドサマーシトラス！
Please listen to "Midsummer Citrus"!
みんな盛り上がっていこう！
Let's get hyped, everyone!
焼けつくような日差し
The scorching sunlight
水面に浮かぶスパンコール
Sequins floating on the water's surface
発色 夏色と逆光の裏側で
On the flip side of bright summer colors and backlighting
あの日の青春を呼び起こしている
Evoking the youth of that day
目に映る像を捲って
Flipping through the images reflected in my eyes
裸足で走ってる 砂の上
Running barefoot on the sand
ガラスの縁で回り回る 輝く瑠璃色のビー玉
Spinning on the edge of the glass, a shining lapis lazuli marble
何だかその笑顔と 紙一重だな
Somehow, it's a paper-thin difference from that smile
フレームを覗けば ノンフィクション
Peering into the frame, it's non-fiction
彩りに翻弄されたメモリー
A memory toyed with by colors
リセットなんてできないから
Because we can't just reset it
Love, Respect, Trust, Us, You and I
踊ってミッドサマー
Dance, Midsummer
アルゴリズムの中
Within the algorithm
瞬速でダビングして
Dubbing at instant speed
切り取ってきたアイラ
This love we captured
これが喜怒哀楽
This is our emotions
二度とは忘れないように
So we'll never forget it again
Lemon, Lime, Orange 君と一生分の思い出
Lemon, lime, orange, a lifetime of memories with you
何気ない一日が One of a kind
A casual, ordinary day is one of a kind
よし、じゃんけんしよ！
Alright, let's do rock-paper-scissors!
最初はグー、じゃんけんぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
勝ったー！ 負けたー！
I won! I lost!
氷が解けて波打つマドラー
The ice melts, a swirling muddler
魔法の杖がわりのマドラー
A muddler serving as a magic wand
ボトルのコークスクリュー回そう
Let's turn the bottle's corkscrew
香る柑橘系のフレーバー
The aroma of citrus flavor
爽やかな気流に乗って
Riding on a refreshing breeze
波の帰りを 見守ってる ビーチサイド
Watching the waves recede by the beachside
あどけない面影に焦がれ
Yearning for an innocent vestige
微かに触れそうな指先
Fingertips that almost touch
きらめきで上塗りしてしまう
Painting over it with brilliance
Get back to what you used to be
踊ってミッドサマー
Dance, Midsummer
アルゴリズムの中
Within the algorithm
瞬速でダビングして
Dubbing at instant speed
切り取ってきたアイラ
This love we captured
これが喜怒哀楽
This is our emotions
二度とは忘れないように
So we'll never forget it again
ミッドサマーシトラス おおやー！
Midsummer Citrus, oh yeah!
言ったって We got it, alright, okay
Just like we said, we got it, alright, okay
見ているだけでフリーズしそうな心はまた実り
The heart that seemed to freeze just by watching blooms once again
寝起きの太陽も願ってもない燦燦日和
Even the morning sun brings perfect, sunny weather
白飛びしそうなハート
A heart that's about to overexpose
目映いのは
What shines so bright
ReGLOSSのせい！
Is because of ReGLOSS!
踊ってミッドサマー
Dance, Midsummer
アルゴリズムの中
Within the algorithm
瞬速でダビングして
Dubbing at instant speed
切り取ってきたアイラ
This love we captured
これが喜怒哀楽
This is our emotions
二度とは忘れないように
So we'll never forget it again
Lemon, Lime, Orange 君と一生分の思い出
Lemon, lime, orange, a lifetime of memories with you
何気ない一日が One of a kind
A casual, ordinary day is one of a kind
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
10月16日、みんなと会えるの楽しみにしているよー！
We're looking forward to seeing everyone on October 16th!
有明アリーナも、配信も、全力で盛り上げます！
We'll get Ariake Arena and the stream hyped up with all our might!
これからもお楽しみに！
Please look forward to what's coming next!
セカンドアルバムもたくさん聴いてください！
Please listen to our second album a lot!
ということで、せーの、ReGLOSSでした！バイバーイ！
And with that... ready, set... We were ReGLOSS! Bye-bye!
現地でお会いしましょう！
Let's meet at the venue!